<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Men &#8211; Urban Utopia</title>
	<atom:link href="https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product-tag/men/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/</link>
	<description>Craft Your Unique Urban Sanctuary.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 19:30:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>THE NORTH FACE Half Dome T-Shirt</title>
		<link>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/the-north-face-half-dome-t-shirt/</link>
					<comments>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/the-north-face-half-dome-t-shirt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rajnair]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/?post_type=product#038;p=31</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Never Stop Exploring with thoughtful features that help you go further — set-in sleeves provide a natural shape with a tailored look while a rib knit crewneck collar offers premium comfort and durability for lasting wear.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This soft, durable, light-weight tee delivers cozy comfort for nights around the campfire. Easy to wear and care for, you&#8217;ll love the effortless look and feel anywhere you go.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/the-north-face-half-dome-t-shirt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>THE NORTH FACE Men&#8217;s Hoodie</title>
		<link>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/the-north-face-mens-hoodie/</link>
					<comments>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/the-north-face-mens-hoodie/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rajnair]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/?post_type=product#038;p=30</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For those who wake up before sunrise or those who love to relax after an adventure from dawn to sunset,...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For those who wake up before sunrise or those who love to relax after an adventure from dawn to sunset, our beloved hoodie is ideal to wear when the air is fresh. Available in a variety of colours and embroidered with The North Face® logo for a &#8216;casual explorer&#8217; look.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/the-north-face-mens-hoodie/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Short Sleeve T-Shirt</title>
		<link>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/short-sleeve-t-shirt/</link>
					<comments>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/short-sleeve-t-shirt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rajnair]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/?post_type=product#038;p=20</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elevate your urban look by pairing the Urban Utopia Signature Men's T-Shirt with your favorite denim or joggers. Embrace the cityscape vibe with layered jackets or keep it casual with shorts on warmer days.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the essence of urban living with our Urban Utopia Signature Men&#8217;s T-Shirt. Unveiling a harmonious blend of style and comfort, this tee stands as a testament to the modern man&#8217;s pursuit of a utopian wardrobe.</p>
<p><strong>Key Features:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Signature Urban Design:</strong> The Urban Utopia logo takes center stage, an emblem of the metropolitan allure infused into every stitch of this classic men&#8217;s T-shirt.</li>
<li><strong>Supreme Comfort:</strong> Luxuriate in the plush feel of our premium cotton blend, offering unrivaled softness against your skin for a truly indulgent wearing experience.</li>
<li><strong>Versatile Style:</strong> From downtown strolls to rooftop gatherings, the Urban Utopia Signature T-Shirt effortlessly transitions, epitomizing the versatile elegance synonymous with urban living.</li>
<li><strong>Tailored Urban Fit:</strong> Impeccably tailored to complement the urban silhouette, this T-shirt effortlessly merges comfort with a dash of metropolitan flair.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/short-sleeve-t-shirt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Fashion Jacket</title>
		<link>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/black-fashion-jacket/</link>
					<comments>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/black-fashion-jacket/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rajnair]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 13:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/?post_type=product#038;p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pair the Onyx Elegance Black Jacket with jeans for a casual-chic look or layer it over a dress for a more refined ensemble. Whether you're heading to the office or a night out, this jacket is your go-to piece for understated sophistication.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elevate your style with our Onyx Elegance Black Jacket, a versatile wardrobe essential that seamlessly blends fashion and function. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, this jacket boasts a modern silhouette and timeless appeal.</p>
<p><strong>Key Features:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Classic Black Hue:</strong> The deep onyx black color adds a touch of sophistication, making it a versatile piece for various occasions.</li>
<li><strong>Premium Quality:</strong> Made from high-quality materials, our black jacket is designed for both style and comfort, ensuring you look sharp while feeling at ease.</li>
<li><strong>Versatile Design:</strong> From casual outings to formal gatherings, the Onyx Elegance Jacket effortlessly transitions with your lifestyle, making it a must-have in any wardrobe.</li>
<li><strong>Tailored Fit:</strong> The jacket is meticulously tailored to provide a flattering fit, accentuating your silhouette for a polished look.</li>
<li><strong>Functional Details:</strong> Thoughtful details like zippered pockets and a sleek front closure enhance both style and functionality, offering practicality without compromising on elegance.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rajnair01.github.io/UrbanUtopia/product/black-fashion-jacket/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
